Ladies and gentlemen, I am a male, a rhino. Nice to meet you.
I am Kamiki. Good evening.
Today, we're doing a location shoot.
What? What is this place? For those of you who thought we were riding something, you are correct.
This time, we are riding on a tramcar wrapped in Lanman.
It's great.
I'm all alone, and I'm lonely.
I can't do without him.
So let's invite him!
Now, my guest is C-33!
Hello!
Hello on YouTube!
Yay!
Now, we're in the middle of Ranmon.
Ranmon. Takeo and Mantaro.
So, this time...
I don't mean to ramble on and on, but...
I'm having a bit of a screen malfunction right now.
So, are you calling me now?
I'm calling you now?
I'm going to post a question on Twitter now.
I'm going to post a question on my Twitter.
So, okay?
Let's go!
Yeah!
I posted the tweet.
What do you think?
Tweet sent.
What if it's zero or something?
Sad.
Wow!
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming!
Quick question.
How well do you know Kamiki?
Well, it's hard to say how well.
How well?
How well do you know each other?
Well..,
I do a lot of things, Kamiki.
I know a lot of things.
I know a lot of things. My impression is that Ryu doesn't hang out with people in private.
There are many people I get along with, but I don't get the impression that they get together privately to do anything.
Well, I guess I do something in my private life.
Now, let's find out what you like about Kamikiryutsuke. No, this is embarrassing.
Well, he is cheerful.
That's the best. Also, I was really surprised. People don't usually notice Kamikiryuutske, but he is so friendly that it's not true.
He is so friendly. He is friendly to everyone. I'm so happy. I'm so glad. He is very friendly.
That's what Kamikiryutsuke doesn't have. He is cheerful and friendly.
And then there's the kindness.
I'm glad to hear that. I'm glad. He is considerate and always looks around him.
He always listens to and talks to people onsite. That makes me happy. That's the kind of guy he is.
By the way, I have only one favorite thing about Shi-chan. All of them!
That makes me so happy.
Yes!
It was totally a staff company, wasn't it?
It was a staff company.
I'll keep it as a memory.
Yay!
I've heard today that there's too much of a ban on bakbakbakbak!
I was just on Doster today.
Doster was on the show.
Baki-baki-baki-baki-baki-baki-baki-baki-baki-baki-baki-baki-baki-baki-baki
We had to chant it, didn't we?
I think you're setting the bar a little too high.
It's not unexpected?
No, it's not a surprise.
You're not happy with yourself.
I'm not a woman.
Jonocchi's Jonocchi.
He's a little too muscular for my taste.
But Lium, you're more muscular than I thought.
No, no, no. I'm supple.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Is it difficult for you?
Well, you know, it's difficult for everyone.
I don't know, it's just that I don't feel the same way about Liu as you do.
That's true.
I memorize by sound and remember only on the spot.
But Liu remembers by how many syllables.
He says, "Oh, yes, this is the way to say it, so this is the way to say it," and so on.
I think it's great that Liu can improvise more easily, and I think it's great that he can do it in a certain number of steps.
I'm used to saying "this" in certain situations, so I can't go wrong.
I'm still working on it.
Five or six weeks are on the air...
Yes, yes.
But we're filming further in the future.
16 weeks, 17 weeks... 10 years before that.
It's becoming more and more like a hometown.
I'm glad you said that.I'm glad you said that.
That's great, but Nishimura Sensei, who speaks in dialect, too
Nishi
Nishi is also great
The more we both do
The more we do, the better we get. I'm glad you praise us.
Thank you.
That's what I'm talking about!
I want to hear about how you laughed so hard at the suspension.
What?
Well, let's see...
We do the same play a few times.
Basically, we do a test every time.
Once, to check the camera.
And we do our own checks.
But if we do it too many times
People don't need to check anymore.
What? Can't we just go to the next show?
The director can just go on the next show, right?
Oh, so we'll go to the real test?
Then we'll give the test for the next round and go to the next round.
And so on.
There's a quote from one of his descendants.
On the day of the show
It's important to call out to the audience.
One of the female supervisors, who was the chief of staff, said...
Then the chief female director says, "Okay, everyone, let's go on stage.
Then, the staff called and said, "Okay, let's go on stage.
And we said the same thing.
And then she says, "Well, we're going on the air during the test.
And then we'll make it a real test.
And then...
What? What?
Who's drunk on the day of the test?
I hope so.
The real test! And then we're going to the real test.
Who's drunk on test day?
I hope so.
That's terrible.
You're a terrible actor.
I'm not kidding.
I'll sign up for YouTube.
Okay, on the air!
On the air!
But we get along really well.
Including the staff.
We get along really well.
And...
And the three of them are all really supportive of me.
And the director, he's like, "Burn, burn, burn, burn, burn, burn!
That's what I was aiming for.
Yeah, that's what you said from the beginning.
That kind of playfulness.
Even if it was just for fun.
I knew how hard it would be.
The morning drama...
But even in that situation...
"There's a guy who lights up the fire" and he'd giggle.
That kind of light-heartedness.
Light, in a good way.
I wanted that scene.
Mie Hamabe and Yui Saima...
They really laughed at us.
Even though we were just messing around.
I'm so grateful.
They're wonderful people.
There's a show called "TENIMU".
I'll use it.
I went to see it too.
And I really like Myuu.
I was in it, too?
Hey...
Hey, you're not in it.
Oh, you mean Director Tezuka's music.
That music is playing.
"Telethette, telethette, telethette, telethette, telethette.
TeleteTe Telete Telete
I don't know why it started.
Suddenly Ryu said
Hey, Takeo!
"Be a pillar of Minea.
I'm going to be a pillar of Minea.
I started dancing "teletete, teletete, teletete, teletete, teletete, teletete...
And then he started dancing.
And then he told me to be a pillar of everything.
And they're dancing and dancing.
That was funny.
Ikee, eh, chi-zeen.Ike, eh, chi-zeh.
There's a lot to remember.
There's a lot of things.
There's Entwuda Kalayaki.
Entwu da kalayaki.
Entoo da kalayaki.
This, this, this is a very serious scene.
It's all of us.
You don't think we're laughing in the background.
They don't think we're laughing behind their backs, right?
So, since we're here, let's do Entoo da Kalayaki.
That's me.
In three weeks.
In Tokyo with young people...
I don't think I'm this messed up...
Mantana Kalayaki.
At that beef hot pot restaurant...
Mantaro...
I was like, "Oh, he's not here..." and he said, "Oh, he's not here.
I say it in the scene where Mantoro is really pissed off.
I was practicing saying "anta dakarayaki" all the time, and we were talking about how it sounds like English.
I was practicing it for a long time, and we were talking about how it sounds like English.
And we were talking about how it sounded like English, and then we started saying "Entadakarayakee.
But if you listen carefully
The sound is a little bit...
There's another one under the chair for audio.
Please try saying "antadakarayakee" one time.
Antah dakaraya key.
Okay, now the English version.
Antadakarayakee.
Um, well, me and Takeo and...
Um, well, Aya and
Hamabe
Just Hamabe? What beach?
It's all messed up.
Like, well, we're going to create a new era...
But even the rest of the people, they're all so big.
I really thought so.
Each character is a heroine.
They are all heroines, and the work can be seen as a whole even if you look at it with that person in the center.
What do you think Kamiki and Shiz-san have in common that is similar to each other?
I wonder.
At the same time, we sometimes say things that are close to each other.
Oh, we do that. We do that.
I wonder.
You're more together than family.
That's true.
We're together more than anyone else.
We're together all the time.
So, the other day, when we weren't shooting, we hung out, right?
We did, didn't we?
You'll be over there, right?
I know you'll be there.
I can tell, even when we're acting.
Whatever.
I know. Like, don't tell me yet.
You're right.
I've never worn it before.
But now you're putting it on on purpose.
It's just a movement or something.
That's true.
Do you have time to shop?
I do. I'm fine.
How's life? Normal.
Doesn't sound like a normal life, does it?
Think about it, folks... what did this guy do last year before he started filming in the mornings?
He was on Stage 9, traveling around the world, doing hundreds of shows.
He's been on stage 9 for hundreds of shows, and then he comes here without a pass.
We did rehearsals and readings remotely while we were overseas.
Isn't that bad? Yes, it's really bad.
Oh, and I just remembered something... a first episode.
What?
We used to send each other messages like, "Let's work hard," right?
Yeah.
Then, when I was in Taiwan.
Ryu suddenly dropped me a line.
Yeah.
Jun.
Can I call you? He said, "Can I call you for a minute?
I don't know what happened.
Ryu asked me if he could call me. I thought, "I've never heard that before," and I called him.
I called him, and he was always smiling and saying, "Don't worry about it, okay? He's always smiling and saying, "Don't worry about it.
Jun.
I'm so nervous.
It's hard to speak in Tosa dialect.
It's a long shoot and there are a lot of lines.
I don't know what to do.
I'll be fine. I'll talk to Ryu and stuff.
We talked for about two hours.
Anyway, what I wanted to tell you was...
Jun, you haven't practiced your tosa-ben, have you?Jun, you haven't practiced tosa-ben, have you?
No, I practiced tosa-ben first.
You haven't done it yet, right?
No, I haven't. I'm fine.
It was so rare.
I was so heartbroken.
I've never seen Ryu being so sweet.
He's the type of guy who always says, "I'll be fine" and "I'll figure something out.
This is unusual. I thought you were that careful.
I was nervous, and I wanted someone to cheer me up.
I wanted someone to cheer me up. The reason why I was able to do well in Tosabe was partly because I wanted to work hard with June.
I didn't want to lose because June was working so hard, and I wanted to be better than her.
Maybe because we were both like that.
I'm going to practice more because I have that feeling.
I'm going to be better than June.
The sensor was very good. The sensor was very good.
That was really good, but I felt like I wasn't really practicing.
I'm not really practicing.
That was the first time I said that.
I'm going to say it for the first time.